Congrats on reaching
the end of this module.
So what did we learn?
We learned that data plays a
key part in the success of
any organization and it
impacts your role as
a project manager.
We've learned what data is,
the value that data
provides for your projects,
and how it empowers you to
achieve your project's goals.
You learned about the
different types of data,
like metrics and projections,
and how to identify and
discern what information
to watch for and to
communicate to stakeholders.
We also discussed how important
data is to help you make
informed decisions and
showcase areas where
you and your team are
being most effective,
flagging potential risks, and
opportunities to advance.
We reviewed data visualization
and data tools and learned that
facts are usually easier to
remember when there's
a visual alongside it.
We also discussed ways
for you to present all of
your insights to stakeholders,
colleagues, and customers.
So let's pause so you can give
yourself a high five
for coming this far.
Next up, we'll discuss
leadership and the
fundamentals of teamwork.
Keep up the great work,
and we'll meet you there
when you're ready.